Guide to the Arabic Film Poster Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Posters, 1935-2005; Series I
  - Egypt
    - Al-nashshal, 1963 (Box 39)
    - Al-nashshalah, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Al-nazir, 2000 (Box 39)
    - Al-nashshalat al-fatinat, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Amrika shika bika, 1993 (Box 40)
    - Imra'ah bila qayd, 1970 (Box 40)
    - Amirit... hubi ana, 1974 (Box 40)
    - Imbraturiyyat "m", 1972 (Box 40)
    - Imra'ah sayyi'it al-sum'ah, 1972 (Box 40)
    - Imra'ah fi dawwamah [two posters], 1962 (Box 40)
    - Amir al-'arab, 1963 (Box 40)
    - Ummahat fi al-manfa, 1981 (Box 40)
    - Al-yatim... wa al-hub, undated (Box 40)
    - Al-wadi'ah, 1965 (Box 40)
    - Al-wahil, 1987 (Box 40)
    - Al-wafa' al-'azim, 1974 (Box 40)
    - Al-wahim, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Al-wadi al-asfar, 1970 (Box 40)
    - Al-wardah al-hamra', 2001 (Box 40)
    - Irham dumu'i, undated (Box 40)
    - Zalamt ruhi, undated (Box 40)
    - Ihtarisi mina al-hub, 1959 (Box 41)
    - Ibtisamah fawqa shifah tartajif, 1985 (Box 41)
    - Ahlam hind wa kamilyah, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Isha'it hub, 1960 (Box 41)
    - Ahlam al-rabi', 1955 (Box 41)
    - Arba'ah fi muhimmah rasmiyyah, 1987 (Box 41)
    - A'az al-habayib, undated (Box 41)
    - Ibnati wa al-dhi'b [two posters], 1977 (Box 41)
    - Anf wa thalath 'uyun, undated (Box 41)
    - Ana wa ibnati wa al-hub, 1974 (Box 41)
    - Imra'ah tadfa'u al-thaman, 1993 (Box 41)
    - Amir al-zalam, 2002 (Box 41)
    - Imra'ah... 'ala al-hamish, 1963 (Box 41)
    - Um al-'arusah, 1962 (Box 41)
    - Imra'ah wa khamsit rijal, 1997 (Box 41)
    - Adhkiya'... lakin aghbiya', 1977 (Box 42)
    - Ihna bitu' al-is'af, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Arduna al-khadra', 1956 (Box 42)
    - i'dam mayyit, 1985 (Box 42)
    - Abi fawqa al-shajarah, 1969 (Box 42)
    - Ijazah bi al-'afiyah, 1965 (Box 42)
    - Asrar al-banat, 1969 (Box 42)
    - Ashraf khati'ah, 1973 (Box 42)
    - Isma'il yasin fi al-ustul, 1957 (Box 42)
    - Isma'il yasin fi al-tayaran, 1959 (Box 42)
    - Isma'il yasin fi al-jaysh, 1955 (Box 42)
    - Ibn al-shaytan, 1969 (Box 42)
    - Isma'il yasin fi dimashq, 1958 (Box 42)
    - Abu ahmad, 1960 (Box 42)
    - Ihtarisi min al-rijal ya mama, 1975 (Box 42)
    - Iskandariyyah... layh?, 1979 (Box 43)
    - Azmit sakan, 1972 (Box 43)
    - Ishtibah, 1991 (Box 43)
    - Abu al-dahab, 1996 (Box 43)
    - Ughniyah 'ala al-mamar, 1972 (Box 43)
    - Azwaj ta'ishun, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Aswar al-madabigh, undated (Box 43)
    - Aqwa min al-hayat, 1960 (Box 43)
    - Akhir fursah, 1962 (Box 43)
    - Ijazit nus al-sanah, 1962 (Box 43)
    - Ihtaris mi al-khat, 1984 (Box 43)
    - Ibtisamah... wahidah takfi, 1978 (Box 43)
    - Abu hadid, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Akhir al-'unqud, 1966 (Box 43)
    - Ikhwatuh al-banat, 1976 (Box 43)
    - I'tida', 1982 (Box 44)
    - Isma'il yasin lilbay', 1958 (Box 44)
    - 4-2-4, undated (Box 44)
    - Idini 'aqlak, 1952 (Box 44)
    - Ard... ard, 1998 (Box 44)
    - Isma'il yasin fi mustashfa al-majanin, 1958 (Box 44)
    - Isma'il yasin fi bayt al-ashbah, 1954 (Box 44)
    - Ibn min fi al-mujtama', undated (Box 44)
    - I'dam qadi, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Abu kartunah, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Ard al-khawf, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Uridu hallan..., 1975 (Box 44)
    - Ihtaris! Nahnu al-majanin, 1981 (Box 44)
    - Armalah wa thalath banat, 1965 (Box 44)
    - Iblis fi al-madinah, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Istiqalit dabit shurtah, 1997 (Box 45)
    - Isma'il yasin tarazan, 1958 (Box 45)
    - Izzay ansak, 1956 (Box 45)
    - Idhkurini, 1978 (Box 45)
    - Izzay al-banat tihibbak, 2003 (Box 45)
    - Ashyak wad fi ruksi, 1999 (Box 45)
    - Aqwa min al-ayyam [two posters], 1979 (Box 45)
    - Ashab wala biznis, 2001 (Box 45)
    - 2 'ala al-tariq, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Ard al-ahlam, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Afwah wa aranib, 1977 (Box 45)
    - Ihdharu hadihi al-mar'ah, 1991 (Box 45)
    - Afrikanu, 2001 (Box 45)
    - Istakuza, 1996 (Box 45)
    - Akhir al-rijal al-muhtaramin, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Al-akhar, 1999 (Box 46)
    - Al-arajuz, 1989 (Box 46)
    - Al-imbraturah, 1999 (Box 46)
    - Al-armalah...wa al-shaytan, 1984 (Box 46)
    - Al-imbrartur, 1990 (Box 46)
    - Al-aqwiya', 1982 (Box 46)
    - Al-insan.. ya'ish marah wahidah, 1980 (Box 46)
    - Al-untha wa al-dhi'ab, 1975 (Box 46)
    - Al-azwaj al-shayatin, 1977 (Box 46)
    - Al-ibn al-mafqud, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Al-akhras, 1979 (Box 46)
    - Al-intifadah, 1987 (Box 46)
    - Al-irhab wa al-kabab, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Al-ab al-shar'i, 1988 (Box 46)
    - Al-aydi al-na'imah, 1963 (Box 46)
    - Al-bidayah, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Al-bulis al-sirri, 1959 (Box 47)
    - Al-banat 'ayzah kidah, 1980 (Box 47)
    - Al-ba'd yadhhab ila al-ma'dhun maratayn [two posters], 1978 (Box 47)
    - Al-badrwn, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Al-bahith 'an al-mata'ib, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Al-i'tiraf, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Al-azwaj wa al-sayf, 1961 (Box 47)
    - Al-ashqiya' al-thalathah, 1962 (Box 47)
    - Muhami fi al-shari', undated (Box 47)
    - Al-aghbiya' al-thalathah, 1990 (Box 47)
    - Al-asil, 1973 (Box 47)
    - Illi... dihik 'ala al-shayatin, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Al-abanda, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Al-irhab, 1989 (Box 47)
    - Al-tajribah al-danimarkiyyah, 2004 (Box 48)
    - Al-tahaddi, 1988 (Box 48)
    - Al-tilmidhah, 1961 (Box 48)
    - Al-banat wa al-sayf, 1960 (Box 48)
    - Al-banat sharbat, 1951 (Box 48)
    - Al-bint illi qalit... la', 1982 (Box 48)
    - Al-bahir biyadhak layh, 1994 (Box 48)
    - Al-birins, 1984 (Box 48)
    - Al-bint al-hilwa al-kaddabah, 1977 (Box 48)
    - Al-bustaji, 1968 (Box 48)
    - Al-ba'id ya'ish maratayn, 1971 (Box 48)
    - Al-bahith 'an fadihah, 1972 (Box 48)
    - Al-batiniyyah, 1980 (Box 48)
    - Al-basha, 1993 (Box 48)
    - Al-banat wa al-hub, 1973 (Box 48)
    - Al-hub kidah, 1961 (Box 49)
    - Al-hub alladhi kan, 1973 (Box 49)
    - Al-hafid, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Al-hub al-da'i', 1970 (Box 49)
    - Al-hamawat al-fatinat, 1953 (Box 49)
    - Al-halal yiksab, 1982 (Box 49)
    - Al-jirah, 1995 (Box 49)
    - Al-jasusah hikmat fahmi, 1994 (Box 49)
    - Al-jaban wa al-hub, 1974 (Box 49)
    - Al-jababirah, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Al-jintil, 1996 (Box 49)
  - Al-ju', 1986
    - Al-jahim, 1980 (Box 49)
    - Al-tha'lab wa al-hirba', 1970 (Box 49)
    - Al-thalathah yuhibunaha, 1965 (Box 49)
    - Al-khid'ah al-khfiyyah, 1979 (Box 50)
    - Al-khatafin, 1972 (Box 50)
    - Al-kharsa', 1961 (Box 50)
    - Al-khuruj min al-jannah, 1967 (Box 50)
    - Al-harrif, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub wa al-ru'ub, 1991 (Box 50)
    - Al-hajar al-dayir, 1992 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub al-awwal, 2000 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub fi al-thallajah, 1993 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub al-samit, 1958 (Box 50)
    - Al-hayat hilwah, 1966 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub al-khalid, 1965 (Box 50)
    - Al-haram, 1965 (Box 50)
    - Al-hub al-akhir, 1959 (Box 50)
    - Al-haqid, 1962 (Box 50)
    - Al-rahibah, 1965 (Box 51)
    - Al-rahmah ya nas, undated (Box 51)
    - Al-rayah hamra, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Al-rasasah latazal fi jaybi, 1974 (Box 51)
    - Al-risalah al-akhirah, 1964 (Box 51)
    - Al-rajul al-majhul, 1965 (Box 51)
    - Al-rida' al-abyad, 1973 (Box 51)
    - Al-dhi'ab, 1982 (Box 51)
    - Al-dhul, 1989 (Box 51)
    - Al-dunya jara fiha ayh, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Al-dakhil, 1967 (Box 51)
    - Al-khtar, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Al-khadimah, 1984 (Box 51)
    - Al-khayt al-rafi', 1971 (Box 51)
    - Al-sahirah al-saghirah, 1963 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawjah 13, 1962 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawaj 'ala al-tariqah al-hadithah, 1968 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawjah al-thaniyah, 1967 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawjah ta'rif akthar, 1986 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawj al-muhtaram, 1977 (Box 52)
    - Al-za'irah, 1972 (Box 52)
    - Al-za'im, 1999 (Box 52)
    - Al-zawj al-'azib, 1966 (Box 52)
    - Al-raqisah wa al-shaytan, 1992 (Box 52)
    - Al-raghbah wa al-daya', 1973 (Box 52)
    - Al-rajul al-thani, 1959 (Box 52)
    - Al-raqisah wa al-siyasi, 1990 (Box 52)
    - Al-raqisah wa al-tabbal, 1984 (Box 52)
    - Al-ru'b, 1969 (Box 52)
    - Al-shaytan yuqadim hallan, 1991 (Box 53)
    - Al-shuj'an al-thalathah [two posters], 1969 (Box 53)
    - Al-shaqiqan, 1965 (Box 53)
    - Al-shak ya habibi, 1979 (Box 53)
    - Al-shawish hasan, 1988 (Box 53)
    - Al-sharabiah, 1987 (Box 53)
    - Al-shayatin fi ijazah, 1972 (Box 53)
    - Al-sajinah 67, 1992 (Box 53)
    - Istub, 1989 (Box 53)
    - Al-sullam wa al-thu'ban, 2001 (Box 53)
    - Al-sarab, 1970 (Box 53)
    - Al-sullam al-khalfi, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Al-sutuh, 1984 (Box 53)
    - Al-sir fi bir, 1953 (Box 53)
    - Al-sadah al-murtashun, 1983 (Box 53)
    - Al-sabir fi al-mallahat, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Al-saqir, 1950 (Box 54)
    - Al-sarkhah, 1991 (Box 54)
    - Al-sa'ayidah jum!, 1989 (Box 54)
    - Al-su'ud ila al-hawiyah, 1978 (Box 54)
    - Al-shayatin al-thalathah, 1964 (Box 54)
    - Al-shumu' al-sawda', 1962 (Box 54)
    - Al-shawari' al-khalfiyyah, 1974 (Box 54)
    - Al-sharidah, 1979 (Box 54)
    - Al-shahhat, 1972 (Box 54)
    - Al-shubbak, 1980 (Box 54)
    - Al-sharih, undated (Box 54)
    - Al-shaqqah min haq al-zawjah, 1985 (Box 54)
    - Al-sharis, 1992 (Box 54)
    - Al-shuttar, 1993 (Box 54)
    - Yawm min 'umri, 1961 (Box 55)
    - Al-'uzzab al-thalathah, 1964 (Box 55)
    - Al-'iqab, 1948 (Box 55)
    - Al-'aqil wa al-mal, 1965 (Box 55)
    - Al-'umir ayyam, 1964 (Box 55)
    - Al-'adhab... imra'ah, 1977 (Box 55)
    - Al-'atabah jazzar..!, 1969 (Box 55)
    - Al-'adhab.. fawqa shifah tabtasim, 1974 (Box 55)
    - Al-'ashiqat, 1974 (Box 55)
    - Al-taghiyah, 1984 (Box 55)
    - Al-tariq ila 'arafat, undated (Box 55)
    - Al-tayyib. al-sharis. al-wahish, 1990 (Box 55)
    - Al-tuyur al-muhajirah, 1979 (Box 55)
    - Al-dahaya, 1975 (Box 55)
    - Al-da'i'ah, 1986 (Box 55)
    - Wahabtuka hayati, 1956 (Box 56)
    - Wa tadhaku al-aqdar, 1985 (Box 56)
    - Wahdah...ba'da wahdah wa nus, 1978 (Box 56)
    - Yahya al-hub, 1938 (Box 56)
    - Ya sadiqi... kam tusawi, 1987 (Box 56)
    - Yawm al-ahad al-dami, 1975 (Box 56)
    - Ya 'azizi kulluna lusus, 1986 (Box 56)
    - Ya rab tubah, 1957 (Box 56)
    - Yumhil wala yhmil, 1978 (Box 56)
    - Yawm bila ghad, 1962 (Box 56)
    - Yawm sa'id, 1940 (Box 56)
    - Yawm mur yawm hilu, 1988 (Box 56)
    - Ya zalimni, 1954 (Box 56)
    - Har jiddan, undated (Box 56)
    - Ya tihib ya tiqib, 1994 (Box 56)
    - Man al-qatil, undated (Box 57)
    - Layta al-shabab, undated (Box 57)
    - Wa tamdi al-ayyam, 1978 (Box 57)
    - Wa mada.. qitaru al-'umir, 1975 (Box 57)
    - Ward wa shuk, 1970 (Box 57)
    - Wala min shaf... wala min diri, 1982 (Box 57)
    - Wa 'ada... al-hub, 1960 (Box 57)
    - Widad al-ghaziyah, 1983 (Box 57)
    - Wa bilwalidayni ihsana, 1976 (Box 57)
    - Wa quyyidat... dida majhul, 1981 (Box 57)
    - Wada'an ila al-abad..., 1976 (Box 57)
    - Wa mina al-hubi ma qatal, 1978 (Box 57)
    - Wa thalithuhum al-shaytan, 1977 (Box 57)
    - Wakalit al-balah, 1982 (Box 57)
    - Watani al-akbar, 1960 (Box 57)
    - Wala 'aza' lil sayyidat, 1979 (Box 57)
    - Wa'd, 1954 (Box 57)
    - Hurub, 1970 (Box 58)
    - Hamsat al-layl, 1975 (Box 58)
    - Hakadha al-ayyam, 1977 (Box 58)
    - Hadha uhibuh... wa hadha uriduh, 1975 (Box 58)
    - Hadha al-rajul uhibuh, 1962 (Box 58)
    - Huda, 1959 (Box 58)
    - Hadiyyah, 1947 (Box 58)
    - Hallu amrika, 2000 (Box 58)
    - Wada'an lil 'uzubiyyah, 1993 (Box 58)
    - Wuhush al-mina', 1983 (Box 58)
    - Wa tammat aqwaluh, 1991 (Box 58)
    - Wahidah biwahidah, 1983 (Box 58)
    - Wara' al-shams, 1978 (Box 58)
    - Wa da'a... hubi hunak, 1982 (Box 58)
    - Nisa' fi al-madinah, 1976 (Box 59)
    - Nar fi sadri, 1963 (Box 59)
    - Arnab, 1983 (Box 59)
    - Nihayit hub, 1957 (Box 59)
    - Nahir al-hayat, 1964 (Box 59)
    - Nihayit al-tariq, 1960 (Box 59)
    - Harib min al-zawaj, 1964 (Box 59)
    - Histirya, 1998 (Box 59)
    - Huwwa fi ayh ?, undated (Box 59)
    - Hammam fi amistirdam, 1999 (Box 59)
    - Huda wa ma'ali al-wazir, undated (Box 59)
    - Hiya... wa al-rijal, 1965 (Box 59)
    - Huwa... wa al-nisa', 1966 (Box 59)
    - Hijrit al-rasul, 1964 (Box 59)
    - Harmunika, 1998 (Box 59)
    - Majlis al-idarah, undated (Box 60)
    - Al-sa'adah al-muharramah, undated (Box 60)
    - Al-khubz al-mur, undated (Box 60)
    - Nida' al-'ushshaq, 1960 (Box 60)
    - Nisa' muharramat, 1959 (Box 60)
    - Naw' min al-nisa', 1978 (Box 60)
    - Nur al-'uyun, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Nazwah, 1996 (Box 60)
    - Nahnu la nazra' al-shuk, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Nar al-shuq, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Nibtidi minayin al-hikayah, 1976 (Box 60)
    - Nihayit al-shayatin, 1970 (Box 60)
    - Nisa' wa dhi'ab, 1960 (Box 60)
    - Nisf 'adhra', 1961 (Box 60)
    - Nisa' al-layl, 1972 (Box 60)
    - Shabab al-yawm, undated (Box 61)
    - Shari'a al-hub, undated (Box 61)
    - Samihni, undated (Box 61)
    - Samarah, 1991 (Box 61)
    - Al-jarimah wa al-'iqab, undated (Box 61)
    - Ana wa qalbi, undated (Box 61)
    - Bafakkar fi illi nasini, undated (Box 61)
    - Ard al-salam, undated (Box 61)
    - Gharam fi al-sahra', undated (Box 61)
    - Hazzak hadha al-usbu', undated (Box 61)
    - Al-hub al-makruh, undated (Box 61)
    - Rabi' al-hub, undated (Box 61)
    - Imra'ah fi dami, undated (Box 61)
    - Al-masajin al-thalathah, undated (Box 61)
    - Sit al-bayt, undated (Box 61)
    - Wa islamah, undated (Box 62)
    - Kifayah ya 'ayn, undated (Box 62)
    - Ana dhanbi ayh, undated (Box 62)
    - Lahin al-wafa', undated (Box 62)
    - Khaltabitah, undated (Box 62)
    - Mau'id gharam, 1956 (Box 62)
    - Isma'il yasin fi jinaynit al-haywanat, undated (Box 62)
    - Man bila khati'ah, undated (Box 62)
    - Da'irit al-intiqam, undated (Box 62)
    - Ya halawit al-hub, undated (Box 62)
    - Al-namrud, 1956 (Box 62)
    - Mamnu' al-hub, 1942 (Box 62)
    - Al-mustahtir, undated (Box 62)
    - Al-manzil qum 13, undated (Box 62)
    - Al-malak al-zalim, undated (Box 62)
    - Mau'd ma'a al-sa'adh, undated (Box 62)
    - Laylah min 'umri, undated (Box 62)
    - Sawt min al-madi, undated (Box 62)
  - Iraq
    - Al-qadisiyyah, undated (Box 63)
    - Al-sayyid al-mudir, 1991 (Box 63)
    - Buyut fi dhalika al-ziqaq, 1977 (Box 63)
    - Hamad wa hamdun, 1986 (Box 63)
    - Al-munafidhun, 1987 (Box 63)
    - Yawm akhar, 1979 (Box 63)
    - Al-ra'is, 1977 (Box 63)
    - Sakhab al-bahir, 1987 (Box 63)
    - Al-bahithun, 1979 (Box 63)
    - Hub fi baghdad, 1987 (Box 63)
    - 100%, undated (Box 63)
    - 'Amarah 13, 1987 (Box 63)
    - Babil habibati, 1988 (Box 63)
    - Iftarid nafsak sa'id, undated (Box 63)
    - Badi'ah, undated (Box 63)
    - Fayiq yatazawwaj, 1984 (Box 63)
    - Al-'ashiq, 1985 (Box 63)
    - Al-mas'alah al-kubra, 1983 (Box 63)
  - Jordan
    - Kifah hata al-tahrir, undated (Box 64)
    - Al-tariq ila al-quds, undated (Box 64)
  - Lebanon
    - Al-jababirah, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Al-ja'izah al-kubra, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Al-bayt al-zahir, undated (Box 64)
    - Al-badawiyyah al-'ashiqah, 1963 (Box 64)
    - Al-bank, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Al-i'sar, 1993 (Box 64)
    - Al-asirah, 1973 (Box 64)
    - Al-akhras wa al-hub, 1966 (Box 64)
    - Abtal wa nisa', 1969 (Box 64)
    - Abu salim fi al-madinah, undated (Box 64)
    - Ajmal ayyam hayati, 1974 (Box 64)
    - Layali al-sharq [two posters], 1965 (Box 64)
    - Al-infijar, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Al-qannas [two posters], undated (Box 64)
    - Al-malja', 1980 (Box 64)
    - Al-'asal wa al-mur, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Al-tarid, 1969 (Box 65)
    - Al-ta'r al-dhahabi, 1993 (Box 65)
    - Al-shaykhah, 1993 (Box 65)
    - Al-sharidan [two posters], 1965 (Box 65)
    - Al-sum al-abyad, 1961 (Box 65)
    - Al-ru'ya, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Al-rajul al-samid [two posters], 1975 (Box 65)
    - Al-rahinah, 1966 (Box 65)
    - Al-dallu'ah, 1966 (Box 65)
    - Al-hasna' wa al-nimir, 1972 (Box 65)
    - Al-hub al-kabir, undated (Box 65)
    - Al-janub al-tha'r, 1985 (Box 65)
    - Al-jihah al-khmisah, 1984 (Box 65)
    - Al-jazirah al-muharramah, 1999 (Box 65)
    - Anta 'umri, undated (Box 66)
    - Ivanova, 2000 (Box 66)
    - Al-mamar al-akhir, 1981 (Box 66)
    - Al-marmurah, 1985 (Box 66)
    - Al-mujazif, 1983 (Box 66)
    - Al-mutawahhishun, 1982 (Box 66)
    - Al-milyunayrah [two posters], 1965 (Box 66)
    - Al-layl al-akhir, 1982 (Box 66)
    - Al-layali al-hilwah, 1966 (Box 66)
    - Al-lis al-zarif [two posters], 1968 (Box 66)
    - Al-qahirun, 1966 (Box 66)
    - Al-qarar [two posters], 1981 (Box 66)
    - Al-fatinah wa al-mughamir, 1985 (Box 66)
    - Al-ghajariyyah al-'ashiqah, 1972 (Box 66)
    - Al-'amya', 1969 (Box 66)
    - Bi'amr al-hub, 1965 (Box 67)
    - Badawiyyah fi roma, 1965 (Box 67)
    - Bint al-shaykh, 1970 (Box 67)
    - Bi't hayati, undated (Box 67)
    - Bint 'antar [two posters], 1964 (Box 67)
    - Bulbul min libnan [two posters], 1982 (Box 67)
    - Ana al-radar, 1968 (Box 67)
    - Ayyam al-lulu, 1986 (Box 67)
    - Ayyam fi landn, undated (Box 67)
    - Imra'ah likul al-rijal, undated (Box 67)
    - Ana 'antar, 1964 (Box 67)
    - Amwaj, 1970 (Box 67)
    - Idak 'an mirati, 1968 (Box 67)
    - 1+1, undated (Box 67)
    - Ahlan bil hub [two posters], 1968 (Box 67)
    - Shati' al-hub, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Shari' al-dabab, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Shadiyit al-jabal, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Safar barlik, undated (Box 68)
    - Zinar al-nar, undated (Box 68)
    - Rimal min dhahab, 1967 (Box 68)
    - Rajul la ya'rif al-khawf, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Sharbil, undated (Box 68)
    - Hikayit gharam, 1963 (Box 68)
    - Hubi alladhi la yamut, 1984 (Box 68)
    - Hurub saghirah, 1982 (Box 68)
    - Hasna' al-badiyah, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Habibati, 1974 (Box 68)
    - Jitar al-hub, 1975 (Box 68)
    - Badawiyyah fi baris, 1964 (Box 68)
    - Funduq al-sa'adih, 1968 (Box 69)
    - Fatinat al-jamahir, 1964 (Box 69)
    - Funduq al-ahlam [two posters], 1967 (Box 69)
    - Gharam fi istanbul, undated (Box 69)
    - 'Antar yaghzu al-sahra', 1969 (Box 69)
    - 'Arus al-bahir, 1984 (Box 69)
    - 'Asifah 'ala al-batra, 1967 (Box 69)
    - 'Awdit al-batal, 1983 (Box 69)
    - 'Antar fi bilad al-ruman, 1974 (Box 69)
    - 'Itab, 1966 (Box 69)
    - 'Adhab al-ummahat, 1982 (Box 69)
    - 'Iqd al-lu'lu' [two posters], 1964 (Box 69)
    - Tariq al-khataya, 1968 (Box 69)
    - Sah al-num, undated (Box 69)
    - Shaytan al-busfur, undated (Box 69)
    - Ma'bad al-hub, 1961 (Box 70)
    - Liqa' al-ghuraba', 1971 (Box 70)
    - Liman yughani al-hub, 1991 (Box 70)
    - Lama hakayit maryam, undated (Box 70)
    - Libnan 'ishiq man?, undated (Box 70)
    - La'ib al-kurah, undated (Box 70)
    - Lu'bit al-haz, 1968 (Box 70)
    - Karam al-hawa, 1970 (Box 70)
    - Kuluna fida'iyyun, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Kalam fi al-hub, 1973 (Box 70)
    - Qitat shari' al-hamra, 1972 (Box 70)
    - Qafzit al-mut [two posters], 1983 (Box 70)
    - Firsan al-gharam, 1968 (Box 70)
    - Fidaki ya filastin, 1969 (Box 70)
    - Nisa' fi khatar, 1981 (Box 71)
    - Nar al-hub, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Naji al-'ali, 1991 (Box 71)
    - Nagham fi hayati, 1974 (Box 71)
    - Nisa' bila ghad, undated (Box 71)
    - Mashakil al-banat, 1969 (Box 71)
    - Maryam al-khati'ah, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Mawwal, 1966 (Box 71)
    - Maw'id ma'a al-hub, 1982 (Box 71)
    - Man yutfi' al-nar, 1982 (Box 71)
    - Misk wa 'anbar, undated (Box 71)
    - Maw'id fi bayrut, 1966 (Box 71)
    - Malikit al-hub, 1972 (Box 71)
    - Mughamarat shushu, 1968 (Box 71)
    - Mister gold, 1993 (Box 71)
    - Wadi al-maut, 1968 (Box 72)
    - Wulidtu min jadid, 1965 (Box 72)
    - Wada'an ya faqr, 1966 (Box 72)
    - Watan fawqa al-jirah, 1965 (Box 72)
    - Hamsat al-shaytan, 1969 (Box 72)
  - Syria
    - Ma yatlubuhu al-mustami'un, undated (Box 73)
    - Banat al-isti'rad, undated (Box 73)
    - Al-farah, undated (Box 73)
    - Ya layl ya 'ayn, undated (Box 73)
    - Man yuhibu al-faqir, undated (Box 73)
    - Al-sa'alik [two posters], undated (Box 73)
    - Fatayat ha'irat, undated (Box 73)
    - 'A'id ila hayfa, undated (Box 73)
    - Bint sharqiyyah, undated (Box 73)
    - Al-tha'lab [two posters], 1971 (Box 73)
    - Wahid za'id wahid, undated (Box 73)
    - Ghawwar masih al-ahdhiyah [three posters], undated (Box 73)
    - Al-tahin al-aswad, undated (Box 74)
    - Al-sadiqan, undated (Box 74)
    - Al-zawaj 'ala al-tariqah al-mahaliyyah [two posters], 1978 (Box 74)
    - Al-ra'iyah al-hasna', undated (Box 74)
    - Al-rajul ala-munasib [two posters], 1969 (Box 74)
    - Al-khati'un, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Al-hub al-haram [two posters], 1977 (Box 74)
    - Al-hudud, 1984 (Box 74)
    - Al-itijah al-mu'akis, 1975 (Box 74)
    - Al-intiqam huban, undated (Box 74)
    - Ahlam al-madinah, 1984 (Box 74)
    - Abu 'antar bund, undated (Box 74)
    - Al-nassabin al-thalathah, undated (Box 75)
    - Al-mughamarah, 1974 (Box 75)
    - Al-matlub rajul wahid, undated (Box 75)
    - Al-misyadah, 1979 (Box 75)
    - Al-makhdu'un, 1973 (Box 75)
    - Al-muzayyafun [two posters], undated (Box 75)
    - Al-layal, 1993 (Box 75)
    - Al-kumbars, 1993 (Box 75)
    - Al-kadimun mina al-bihar, 1977 (Box 75)
    - Al-qal'ah al-khamisah, 1979 (Box 75)
    - Al-fakh, 1979 (Box 75)
    - Al-filastini al-tha'ir, undated (Box 75)
    - Al-fahid, 1972 (Box 75)
    - Al-'alam sanit 2000, 1972 (Box 75)
    - Turab al-ghuraba', 1998 (Box 76)
    - Banat lilhub [two posters], undated (Box 76)
    - Basimah bayna al-dumu', 1985 (Box 76)
    - Baqaya suwar, 1979 (Box 76)
    - Banat akhir zaman, undated (Box 76)
    - Banat al-karatayh, 1986 (Box 76)
    - Ah... ya bahir, 1993 (Box 76)
    - Amut maratayn wa uhibbak, undated (Box 76)
    - Imra'ah taskun wahdaha, 1971 (Box 76)
    - Imra'ah min nar, 1972 (Box 76)
    - Imra'ah birasim al-bay', 1985 (Box 76)
    - Imbraturiyyat ghawwar, 1982 (Box 76)
    - Al-nassabin al-khamasah, 1974 (Box 76)
    - Al-nassabin, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Rihlit hub wa 'adhab, undated (Box 77)
    - Rasa'il shafahiyyah, 1991 (Box 77)
    - Ru'a halimah, undated (Box 77)
    - Rihlit hub, 1972 (Box 77)
    - Rihlit 'adhab [two posters], 1974 (Box 77)
    - Dhikra laylit hub [two posters], undated (Box 77)
    - Khymit karakuz, 1974 (Box 77)
    - Khayyat lilsayyidat [two posters], 1969 (Box 77)
    - Hub lilhayat, 1983 (Box 77)
    - Habibi majnun jiddan, undated (Box 77)
    - Hub wa karatayh, undated (Box 77)
    - Hasna' wa 3 'uyun, 1975 (Box 77)
    - Jazirit al-nisa', undated (Box 77)
    - Thalath 'amaliyyat dakhil filastin, 1969 (Box 77)
    - Shirwal wa mini jub [two posters], 1973 (Box 78)
    - Shabab fi mihnih [two posters], 1972 (Box 78)
    - Shanaw, undated (Box 78)
    - Shaytan al-jazirah, 1978 (Box 78)
    - Shaqqah wa milyun miftah, 1972 (Box 78)
    - Sa'i al-barid, 1977 (Box 78)
    - Sirb al-abtal, undated (Box 78)
    - Samak bala hasak [two posters], 1977 (Box 78)
    - Sawwaqit al-taksi, 1989 (Box 78)
    - Sultanah, 1966 (Box 78)
    - Zawjati mina al-hibiz [two posters], 1973 (Box 78)
    - Zawaj bi al-ikrah [two posters], 1973 (Box 78)
    - Ghizlan [two posters], 1969 (Box 79)
    - Gharamiyat khassah [two posters], 1974 (Box 79)
    - Ghabah mia al-dhi'ab, 1977 (Box 79)
    - Ghabit al-dhi'ab, undated (Box 79)
    - Gharam al-muharrij, 1976 (Box 79)
    - 'Awdit hamidu, 1971 (Box 79)
    - 'Ushshaq 'ala al-tariq, 1977 (Box 79)
    - 'Ushshaq, 1972 (Box 79)
    - 'Arus min dimashq, 1975 (Box 79)
    - 'Irs al-tahaddi, 1978 (Box 79)
    - Su'ud al-matar, 1995 (Box 79)
    - Shaqqah lilhub [two posters], undated (Box 79)
    - Shay' ma yahtariq, 1993 (Box 79)
    - Nisa' lilshita' [two posters], 1974 (Box 80)
    - Muhimmah rasmiyyah, 1975 (Box 80)
    - Maqlab hub, 1972 (Box 80)
    - Liqa' fi tadmur, 1973 (Box 80)
    - Layl al-rijal, 1976 (Box 80)
    - La tatrukni wahdi, 1973 (Box 80)
    - Kafrun, 1990 (Box 80)
    - Qatil... 'an tariq al-tasallul, 1982 (Box 80)
    - Qahir al-fada', 1975 (Box 80)
    - Fatinat al-sahra', 1974 (Box 80)
    - Fursan al-tahrir, 1974 (Box 80)
    - Fida'iyun hata al-nasir, undated (Box 80)
    - Ghawwar jayms bund, 1974 (Box 80)